Hello! My name is: Shannon McGarr

DESIGNER OVERVIEW: Throughout my 20 years in design I've acquired a very specific set of skills, experiences, and perspective that compliment my arsenal of superpowers, all of which set me apart from my peers in the industry. I look forward to having an opportunity to demonstrate how I can be an asset and we can crush the competition together! **MY "WHY":** To encourage, support & empower others so that they can improve their lives and achieve their goals.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS:

- Collaborative
- Problem Solver
- Detail Oriented
- Organized
- Accountable
- Effective Communicator
- Self-Starter
- Consistent
- Objective
- Growth Mindset

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

- Illustrator
- PLM, NGC, SDMS
- Photoshop
- Word
- In DesignMac & PC
- Excel
- ExcelPowerPoint
- CLO
- Spark
- Conceptboard
- Miro

Let's design stuff together!

EDUCATION:

California Design College

Los Angeles, CA

Diploma in Computer Aided Design

Graduated Magna Cum Laude, June 2004

Western Institute of Science & Health

Rohnert Park, CA

Certificate in Massage Therapy

June 2002

FiDM

Los Angeles, CA

A.A. in Fashion Design

Graduated Cum Laude, June 2001

ADDITIONAL CERTIFICATIONS:

Photographer's Assistant, Drafter (Architectural), Brake/Front End Repairman, Massage Therapist, B.E.A.M

A FEW FUN FACTS:

- I had 3 professional certifications prior to graduating High School.
- I spent 3 1/2 yrs as an expat in South Korea for Target
- I have a Frenchie named Mugi & a Pug named Oggi
- I've recently taken on new hobbies such as playing the Banjo, Krav Maga, & Roller Derby.
- The last book I read was *Think and Grow Rich* written by Napoleon Hill.
- One of my favorite quotes is: "You miss 100% of the shots you don't take." Wayne Gretzky

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Target

Minneapolis, MN

February 2013 – Currently Employed

Sr. Product Designer, AIM Girls & Kids' Basics

March 2018 - Current Position

Sr. Innovation Designer, Target+Lab

February 2015 - March 2018

Designer, ITB (Circo | Cherokee)

February 2013 – February 2015

Pro Unlimited - Mattel

El Segundo, CA

Graphic Designer, Creative Vision Team

February 2012 – January 2013

Jerry Leigh

Van Nuys, CA

Apparel Designer, Girls Licensed & Specialty

November 2009 – October 2011

Warnaco - Speedo USA

Los Angeles, CA

Swimwear Designer, Girls & Begin to Swim

October 2006 - November 2009

The Children's Place - Disney Stores

Pasadena, CA

Asst. Apparel Designer, Newborn & Basics

January 2005 - October 2006

FREELANCE:

Multiple Clients

Designer, Apparel & Graphics

Since 2003

Clients Included: Moonlight Graham, Cotton Concepts, Old Toledo (Cecilia Cassini, Quality Meat, & Craftsman), and Jerry Leigh.

PRE-DESIGN CAREER WORK EXPERIENCE:

- The Children's Place Sales Associate 2004-2005
- Trader Joe's Crew Member 2001-2006
- Sarah's Group Homes Caregiver 2000-2001
- Coffee Bean & Tea Leaf Lead Barista 1999-2000
- Urban Outfitters Seasonal Sales Associate 1999
- Bay Buick/GMC Tune-Up Technician 1998-1999 (Yes, I worked on Cars!)







